Guide to the Himalayan Collection Pamphlets and Reports
Yale University Divinity School Library
Himalayan Collection Pamphlets and Reports
1960-2000
RG 211
Yale University Divinity School Library
7
18 boxes
This record group includes pamphlets, reports, and ephemera that were part of the library of the Himalayan Archives Association, a group was formed to coordinate care for the archives of four organizations that had been deposited at the University of Edinburgh in the early 1990s.The Himalayan Mission Archive Collection at the Yale Divinity School Library was formed in 2008 when the archives of the four organizations and their umbrella association were transferred to Yale from the Centre for the Study of World Christianity at the University of Edinburgh.
Himalayan Archives Association
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Himalayan Archives Association, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The Himalayan Archives Association was formed to coordinate care for the archives of four organizations that had been deposited at the University of Edinburgh in the early 1990s. In 2007 when space constraints required the removal of the archives from the University of Edinburgh, the Yale Divinity School Library offered to provide a home for them and the records were received by Yale in 2008.
In addition to the archives of the United Mission to Nepal, International Nepal Fellowship, Central Asia Fellowship, and Nepal Church History Project, the materials received by Yale in 2008 also included the general library of the Himalayan Archives Association. Books in this Himalayan Archives Association have been classified with a local call number system beginning with HC000001. The collection of more than 180 published works can be browsed online via the Orbis "Local call number" search option. The materials in this records group are smaller pamphlets, booklets, reports, and ephemera, which have been described archivally rather than individually cataloged.
Scope and Contents
The pamphlets and reports in this collection relate to Christianity and other issues in the Himalayan region. The topics of the classification categories give a good overview of the types of material included. These are primarily printed materials related to two of the four organizations for which the Himalayan Archives Assocation was an umbrella agency, The United Mission to Nepal, International Nepal Fellowship, as well as topics such as history and politics, culture, government, and development in the Himalayan region, including Nepal, Bhutan, Tibet, and Mongolia.
For related material, see the finding aids for Record Groups 212, 213, 214, and 215, which are the archives of the United Mission to Nepal, International Nepal Fellowship, Central Asia Fellowship, and Nepal Church History Project.
Arrangement
I. Classified Materials
II. Addendum
Missions -- Nepal
- Classified Materials, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The letter classifications utilized in this series were applied to organize pamphlet materials in the Himalayan Collection when it was held at the University of Edinburgh.
  - B: International Nepal Fellowship
    Includes Nepal Evangelistic Band and pre-1900 materials.
    - About the work of Nepal Evangelistic Band (NEB) (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Titles: Nepal Evangelistic Band: What work is it doing?
    - NEB-related narratives, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Titles: Shining Light by Pamela Bolt (1964); The Dream by Patricia Mabey (c.1964); The Church at the Foot of Fish-Tail by Lily O'Hanlon (c.1960); Bhim the Soldier Lad by Lily O'Hanlon (1960); Buddhi Sagar the Christian Farmer by Lily O'Hanlon (c.1965, 2 copies); "Youngest Boy" the Gurkha by Lily O'Hanlon and Hilda Steel (c.1960); The Three Tailors by Margaret Owen (c.1960); Westward from Fishtail by Jean H. Raddon ( c.1962); The Lord gave the Word by Tegwen Scourfield (c.1960) Led into Nepal by Joan Short ( c.1960); The Shining Hospital at the Foot of Fish-Tail by Ruth Watson (c.1960)
    - People of the NEB, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Titles: Patricia Hepworth: Missionar (c.1967); Who's Who? Nepal Evangelistic Band (c.1965 - 2 copies); Photocopy of the diary of Dr. Lily O'Hanlon (1938)
    - Prayer materials, NEB, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Titles: Advance to Baglung: A call to prayer (c.1964); 2 Prayer Cycle pamphlets (1961); 2 Prayer Calendar pamphlets (1961); Will you pray for Debu Singh and his wife Rita Singh?(c.1967)
    - About the work of the International Nepal Fellowship, 1960-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Titles: Making of an Evangelist: Daud Masih (1972); God's Church in Nepal (c.1960) Missionaries are People (c.1960 - 2 copies); What is the INF? (c.1960); General Information: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Wait for me: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Advance in Nepal (c.1970); miscellaneous brochures
    - INF-related narratives, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Titles: Bhim and the Gurkhas by Lily O'Hanlon (1960, reprinted 1972); Life on the Roof by Jean H. Raddon (1977)
    - Medical work, 1960-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Titles: Leprosy Control Programme in West Nepal (1985); Proposed Leprosy Hospital; Ghorahi: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Leprosy Control Project: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Public Health: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Green Pastures: International Nepal Fellowship (c.1960); Leprosy and T.B. Control at Ghorahi (c.1960); 24 English-language health-related brochures
    - Educational work, 1964, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Titles: At School in Nepal by Patricia Mabey (c.1964); Opportunities to Serve in Nepal for Teachers (c.1990)
  - C: United Mission to Nepal
    Official UMN publications (Project publications are on the project files)
    - Educational work, 1987, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Titles: UMN Education Work in Nepal (1987); Aiming at the Future (1992)
    - Engineering and Industrial Development, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Titles: Working Together to Develop Nepal's Resources (1994); Industrial Development Large and Small (1991); UMN Development Work in Nepal (1 copy 1984, 2 copies reprinted in 1985); UMN Development Projects in Nepal (1986); United Mission to Nepal: An Overview of Technical, Industrial, and Training Work in Butwal (c.1985); UMN Engineering & Industrial Development in Nepal (1988)
    - Medical work, 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Titles: UMN Health Services in Nepal (2 copies, 1986); UMN Health Services in Nepal (1989); Caring for Families in Nepal: UMN Health Services (1994)
    - Rural Development, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Titles: UMN Rural Development in Nepal (1 copy 1988 and 1 revised copy 1989); Working Together to Improve the Quality of Life in Nepal (1994)
    - Introducing Nepal and the UMN, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Titles: Introducing Nepal and the UMN (3 copies of printings in 1985, 1986, and 1987); Introducing Nepal and the UMN (1988)
    - Nepal on the Potter's Wheel, 1960-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Titles: Nepal on the Potter's Wheel (1970); Nepal on the Potter's Wheel (1974); Nepal on the Potter's Wheel (1977); Nepal is on the Potter's Wheel (c.1960)
    - Greetings from Nepal, 1963-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      6 books printed in different years entitled "Greetings from Nepal" (1963, 1966, 1972, 2 in 1976, and 1983)
    - History of Nepal, 1961-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Titles: Making a New Nepal (1976); Your Passport to Nepal (c.1970); In Nepal by Ernest W. Oliver (1961); Still in Nepal: The regions beyond missionary union by Ernest W. Oliver (1971); Jai Nepal (c.1990)
    - General Christian Missions in Nepal, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Titles: Christian Missions in Nepal (1961); Informational Notes on Christian Missions in Nepal (October, 1960); Informational Notes on Christian Missions in Nepal (May, 1960); ...use it in service... (1963)
    - UMN - General History and Information, 1977-2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Titles: Your questions answered about the UMN (1989); Your questions answered about the UMN (1988); Nepal (and the UMN) at a glance (1984); U. M. N. 35 Years in Nepal (c.1987); The United Mission to Nepal Briefing Information (1992); The United Mission to Nepal Briefing Information (1990); God's Love at Work in a Changing Land (1993); UMN's First 40 Years: An historical survey (1992); Note page 117: Agenda of the meeting of the Board of Directors of the United Mission to Nepal, April 1-2 (1977); United Mission to Nepal: 1954-2004 (2004); United Mission to Nepal, loose sheets of general information
    - UMN personal narratives, 1960, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Titles: Into Nepal: A vivid account of a recent visit to Nepal's ancient capital by Ernest W. Oliver and Trevor Strong (c.1960); I sat near the "driver's seat" by Jonathan Lindell (c.1977)
    - Nepali pamphlet, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - D: UMN-related
    Written by or about the UMN
    - History of and General Information about Nepal - 1, 1956-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Titles: Nepal: An opened door. God's challenge to this generation by Alan E. Norrish (c.1956); Jai Nepal (1979); Nepal by Tove Madsen (c.1990); Tibet Misjonen: Gjennom 50 Ar 1938-1988 by Asbjorn Voreland (1988)
    - History of and General Information about Nepal - 2, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Titles: Nepal (c.1990) by PCI Overseas; Nepal (c.1991) by PCI Overseas
    - Personal Narratives, 1982, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Titles: Nepal Journey by David J. Warner (1982); Studienreise Nepal by Anneliese Metzler (c.1995)
    - Project Nepal Materials, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Project Nepal pamplets and study guides by the Church Missionary Society (1981)
    - Medical work, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Medical Coorporation [sic] with MIssionary Spirit by Kuni Ito (c. 1981)
    - Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Monthly reports from Okhaldhunga by K. and S. Ito (1981)
    - Nepalese Materials, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Titles: Nepalese book with handwritten English on the back: "Okhalthunga day by day; Our Friends in Nepal by Mr. & Mrs. Ito"
  - E: Eastern Himalayas (Christian)
    Church related materials from the Darjeeling District, Sikkim, and Bhutan.
    - General History, 1960-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Titles: The United Church of Northern India (1968); Christianity in the Eastern Himalayas by L. S. Pradhan (1962); Eastern Himalaya 1870 by Elizabeth G. K. Hewatt (1960); Acts of the Scottish Missionaries in the Eastern Himalayan Region by Panthuk Singh Tingbo (1985); Focus on North East Indian Christianity by O. M. Rao (1994); Introductory Hand-book on Southern Asian Evangelistic Outreach (1992)
    - Personal Narratives, 1946-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Titles: Fire Out of the HImalayan Mountains by S. Sodemba (1990); Christ on Himalayas by T. Satya Rao (1985); Random Notes for Nepal Church History Project (especially 1928-1954) by G. M. Patterson (1986); Ringing of the Gospel-Bells in the Foothills of the Himalayas by Panthuk Singh Tingbo (1985); How I got joy unspeakable and full of glory by Bakht Singh (c.1946)
    - Music articles, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Titles: History is Made as History is Remembered: "Reflecting on the Isai Git Sammelan" by Cindy Perry (1992); Sing Unto the Lord a New Song by Cindy Perry (1992)
    - S. U. M. Institution, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Titles: Sumite (1985); Sumite Centenary Souvenir (1986)
    - Ganga Prasad Pradhan, 1986-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Titles: The Story of Ganga Prasad Pradhan by Jonathan Lindell (1986); Nepali biography of REv. Ganga Prasad Pradhan (1851-1932) by Solon Karthak (c.2000)
    - Church Directories, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Sikkim Church Directory by Daya R. Pradhan (1997)
    - Missionary Biographies, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Graham of Kalimpong by James R. Minto (1974)
    - School materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Centenary Memoirs: Kalimpong Girls High School (1990)
    - Celebratory Church booklets - 1, 1985, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Titles: Presbyterian Free Church Kalimpong Special Anniversary Souvenir (1985); Presbyterian Free Church Central Kalimpong Silver Jubilee 1973-1998 (1998)
    - Celebratory Church booklets - 2, 1991, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Titles: Macfarlane Memorial Church Centenary Kalimpong (1991); Evangelical Presbyterian Church, Sikkim Millennium Celebration Souvenir (2000)
    - Books written in Nepali, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Nepali booklet (1992)
    - Darjeeling Christians material - 1, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Titles: Brief background of the Coming of Christianity in Darjeeling translated by H. C. Pradhan (c.1980); An Enquiry into the Rejection of Their Religious Heritages by Darjeeling Christians by Benjamin Randip Singh Rai (1972)
    - Darjeeling Christians material - 2, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      An Enquiry into the Rejection of Their Religious Heritages by Darjeeling Christians by Benjamin Randip Singh Rai (1972)
  - G: North East India Christianity
    Almost entirely church-related content.
    - Church Origins and History, 1970-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Titles: The Coming of Christianity in manipur (with special reference to the kukis) by Kim Vaiphei (1995); Tribal Ecumenism in North East India: The Christian Role in Solidarity Movements by Frederick S. Downs (1989); The Mizos and the Bible Society by L. B. Thanga (1971); The Christianity Among the Mizos by K. P. Nath (1992); With the Khasis in Northeast India (1980); The Sons of the Soil and Salt of the EARth: A Reflection on the Life and MIssion of the Church with Speical Reference to North-East India by Ernest W. Talibuddin (1993); The Church of Christ in North East India by Frederick S. Downs (1965); Early Christian Contacts with North East India by Frederick S. Downs (1971); Origin and Growth of Christianity among the Borow of Assam by R. N. Mosahary (c.1970); Origins of Christianity in the Garo Hills of Meghalaya by Frederick S. Downs (1972); The Beginning of the Church of Christ in Khasi Hills by Helen Giri (1993)
    - Christian Conversion, 1962, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Titles: Christian Conversion and Transformation in the Hill Areas of Assam by Hamlet Bareh (1962); Are Christian Conversions Communalistic by A. Pushparajan (1984)
    - Christianity and Change, 1962-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Titles: Christianity and Cultural Change Among the Khasis of Meghalaya by O. L. Snaitang (1989); Changes in the LIfe of the Tribal Communities of Assam by E. H. Pakyntein (1962); Christianity and Socio-Cultural Change in the Hill Areas of North East India by Frederick S. Downs (1992); Administrators, Missionaries and a World Turned Upside Down: Christianity as a Tribal Response to Change in North East India by Frederick S. Downs (1981); Christianity as a Tribal Response to Change in Northeast India by Frederick S. Downs (1980)
    - Evangelization, 1979-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Titles: Evangelization Work in Nagaland by J. Puthenpurakal (1983); Evangelisation of the Konyak Nagas: Role of REvered Longri Ao by S. K. Barpujari (c.1981); A Comprehensive Plan for the Evangelization of North East India by Robert Cunville (c.1992); Salesian Contribution to Evangelization in Northeast India (1984); Evangelization of the Konyaknagas (1980); Evangelization in Nagaland and Manipur (1979)
    - Education and Christianity, 1937-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Titles: The Sunday School in the Welsh Presbyterian Mission Field of Assam by Oliver Thomas (1937); Development: Christianity and Education by O. L. Snaitang (c.1992); Missionaries and Education in Mozaroam by Lilrimawia (1984); The First Education Venture in Nagaland by S. K. Barpujari (1980); Role of Missionaries in Mizoram Education by John V. Hluna (c.1983); Beginning of Angami Education by Lanutola Jamir (n.d.)
    - Materials Regarding Women, 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Titles: Impact of the American Missionaries on the Women of North-East India 1836-1900 by Sheila Bora (1990); Female Education in Mizoram by John V. Hluna (1988); The American Baptist Mission - Towards the cause of Garo female education by Milton S. Sangma (1983); Christianity and the Status of Women in the Hill Areas of North East India: Preliminary Reflections by Frederick S. Downs (c.1985); Feminism in the Baptist Church in North East India by Kim Vaiphei (1993); Christian Marriage and the Customary Practices in Manipur by the Joint Women's Programme (1987)
    - Missionaries, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Titles: Missionaries in ARunachal Pradesh During the 18th Century by Thomas Pulloppillil (1982); Recalling the N.E.B. Vision - is it relevant today? by Cindy Perry (1991); Bury My Heart in the Khasi Hills by Elouise Corwin (1980); The Celebration of the Departure of Thomas Jones the First from Liverpool on the 25th November 1840 by R.A. Hughes (1990)
    - Baptist Missions, 1972-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Titles: From Darkness to Light: A story of the Baptist Work among the Konyak Nagas by A. Yanang Konyak (1986); Jorhat - An Educational Centre of the American Baptist Mission by Milton S. Sangma (1993); The New Zealand Baptist Mission and the Beginning of Christian Missionary Activities in Tripura by Mahadev Chakravarti (1989); The Establishment of the American Baptist Assam Mission, 1836-1841 by Frederick S. Downs (1972); Attempts to Christianize the People of Arunachal by the American Baptist Missionaries (1836-1950) by M. S. Sangma (c.1983); American Baptist Mission in North-East India by Milton S. Sangma (1981)
    - Jubilee Souvenirs, 1976-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Titles: Cachar Hill Tribes Synod Souvenir: Diamond Jubilee by Cachar Hill Tribes Synod (1989); The Amazing Guidance of God (Manipur South Christian Diamond Jubilee Souvenir) 1910-1985 by the Independent Church of India (1985); Great Is Thy Faithfulness: KFBC Jubilee Souvenir by Kohima Field Bapstis Centenary Publicity Committee (1985); Mizoram Gospel Centennial Jubilee - 1994 Souvenir by mizoram Presbyterian Church Synod (1994); Golden Jubilee Souvenir 1926-1976 by Presbyterian Church in North East India (1976)
    - Nagaland Materials, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Titles: Nagaland for Christ National Flag (1989); The Joint Statement of: Mr. Isak Chishi Swu, Chairman and Mr. Th. Muivah, General SEcretary, the National Socialist Council of Nagaland (NSCN) (1989); Nagaland the Star of the East by Ellis Murry (1989); An Annual Report of 1991 Nagaland Baptist Church Council (1991)
    - Shillong Materials, 1980-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Titles: Mission Fest 1999: World Outreach "Towards 2000 - The Challenge" Shillong (1999); The Window: Special Issue on North East India by The Study Circle, Shillong (1995) Annual Report 1990: The Bible Society of India, Shillong Auxiliary (1990); Seminar on the Tribes of NOrtheast India - Shillong by C. M. Paul (1980)
    - Mizoram Materials, 1981-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Titles: Mizo Miracle by Baptist Church of Mizoram (c.1995); Mizoram Presbyterian Church SMB (1983); Introducing the Presbyterian Church Synod Mission Board Mizoram (c.1981); Mission for Christ Aizawl Mizoram (1983); A Short History of Nepali Christian Fellowship (1997); Mizoram Today (1994)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1962-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Titles: The Story of Our Foreign Mission (Presbyterian Church of Wales) by John Hughes Morries (1990); Bengal Peoples Profile by National Fellowship (c.1981); Sonderdruck aus Internationales Asienforum: International Quarterly for Asian Studies (1995); Bibliography of Christianity in North-East India by Cindy Perry (c.1995); Colonialism and the Study of Christian Missions in North East India (with special reference to Manipur) by Lal Dena (1982); Primal Vision and Hermeneutics in North East India (1982); New from Many Quarters (1982); Language in the Tribal Churches of North-East India by G. E. Marrison (1962); Historiographical Issues in the Study of the History of Christianity in North East India by Frederick S. Downs (1987)
    - Presbyterian Church in North-East India Booklets, 1974-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Titles: Report of the Consultation on the "Ministry" 16th-17th December 1981 Silchar (1981); Report of the Seminar on Effective Evangelism Among the Other Faiths 28th-30th, April, 1986, Silchar (1986); Report of the Seminar on Evangelism of the Church: 15th-16th November 1978, Silchar (1978); Minutes of the Twenty-Fifth Session held at the Presbyterian Church Haflong, North Cachar Hills, Assam (1982); Minutes of the Twenty Eighth Session held at Lamka, Manipur (1988); Minutes of the Twentyninth Session held at Jatinga, Cachar Hills Tribes Synod, Assam (1990); Minutes of the Twentyfirst Session held at Haflong (1974)
  - H: Other Countries (Christian)
    Church-related material; other areas of India and other lands of the Nepali Diaspora (N.W. India, Bhutan, Tibet)
    - Memoirs, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Sky-High in Tibet by D. Woodward (1990)
    - Statements of Faith, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      My Confession of Faith Wherein I Stand by David Yone Mo (c.1993)
    - Nepalese Materials, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Titles: One book in Nepalese with a blue and brown cover.
  - I: Eastern Himalayas + N. E. India (Secular)
    - Indian Council of Social Science Research Materials, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Titles: Social Movements and the Demand for Autonomy by Gail Omvedt (1993); Bibliography No. 7: Dissertations on North-East India (1989); Bibliography No 8: Articles on North East (1989); North Eastern REgional Centre Annual Report (1994)
    - Pamphlets in Nepali, n.d., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Title: Nepali pamphlet printed by All India Gurkha League (n.d.); Nepali pamphlet with unknown author (1988) Nepali booklet by All India Gurkha League (1943)
    - Articles regarding Sikkim, 1896-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Titles: The Bhot of Northern Sikkim by S. Bose (1966); India's Neighbor: Sikkim by A. Haldar (1960); History of Sikkim by H. H. Risley (1896); Paharia Burial-Customs (British Sikkim) by H. Hosten (1909); The Lepchas of Sikkim reference by Indian Science Congress Proceedings (1934); Ancient Funeral Ceremonies of the Lephcas by R. Nebesky-Wojkowitz (1952); The Lepchas: From Legends to the Present Day by Tanka B. Subba (1985)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1885-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Titles: Gurkha Politics in Assam and its Neighborhood by Bimal J. Dev and Dilip K. Lahiri (n.d.); Shamanism in South Asia: A Preliminary Survey by L. Jones (n.d.); An Aspect of the Nepalese Recruitment from Bhutan to the Assam Rifles by A. C. Sinha (1986); Young Mizo Association: Its history, features, some aspects and its role in transforming the Mizo Society by Sangkima (1985); Description of the Manners, Industries, and Religion of the Tharu and Bogsha Tribes of Upper India by John C. Nesfield (1885)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Titles: Hima-Paryavaran newsletter, v. 1 no.1 by G. B. Pan Institute of Himalayan Environment and Development (1989); Gorkha Association: Shillong Centenary 1886-1986 by Gorkha Association Shillong (1986)
    - Nepalese Books, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Titles: One book in Nepalese
  - J: Other Countries (secular)
    Includes countries of the Nepali Diaspora.
    - History articles, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Titles: South Asia by Cindy Perry (c.1994); Inside Burma: Land of Fear by Carlton UK Television (c.1996)
  - K: Roman Catholics in Nepal and Tibet
    - Mission materials, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Titles: Hindustan-Tibet Mission by Fr. Fulgentius Vannini (1981); Service of Love in a Hindu Kingdom by Maryknoll Fathers and Brothers (1980)
  - L: Nepali Diaspora
    - Bibliographies, c. 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)